nameb.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy policy | NameB

**privacy policy**

Our company respects your privacy at all the time. We have revealed this privacy statement to demonstrate our dedication to our customer.

  * We never give third parties access to your personal details.
  * If you have elected to receive the email from us, we send emails.
  * We will shut down an account that is being used for sending spam.

**Information We collect**

our company requests and collects information from users online in different methods include online forms to order products and services and instances that invite users to volunteer such information.

These data are useful to identify your personality such as your name, email address, postal address, phone numbers, URL, credit card information, and other billing information. We use collected information to contact users online directly.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a part of data that stored on the computer of users online. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session ID cookies get terminated when you close the browser or log out. On the other hand, persistent cookies are stored on the computer for a long time.

**Log Files**

We use log files. The information in the log files include IP addresses, ISP, browser type, platform type, number of clicks to examine trends, gather broad demographic information, administer the site, track user’s movement, date and time, and referring / exit pages.

**How we use and share this information**

We may use the personally identifiable information collected to contact customers regarding services and products offered here to users, trusted affiliates, business partners, and independent contractors.

We use this information and share it to trusted third parties for the purpose of research about the effectiveness of our services, advertising, marketing, and customer reviews.

**Special offers and updates**

Our customers and users receive emails and newsletters with information regarding products, services, and special offers. Our company gives the best chance to opt-out from receiving these communications.

**Service announcements**

It is vital to send out service-related announcement on rare occasions only. For instance, our service is suspended temporarily for maintenance, we send this information. We ensure that these communications are not at all promotional in nature.

**Legally-required disclosures**

We need to disclose the personal information when the law requires it. However, we make every effort to protect the privacy. We disclose information about you when we determine that this disclosure is necessary for the national security and public importance.

**Third party websites**

Our website contains links to other websites. This website is never responsible for such other sites’ privacy practices on the whole. We support you read every website’s privacy statements in-depth.

**Information maintenance**

The information received by this website is saved indefinitely. This information may be stored on different databases directly and indirectly. We use the industry-standard security measures for protecting the confidentiality of information we received.

**Your responsibility**

You are responsible for the ID and passwords of your customer. You have to ensure that you keep them in the safe place. You have to log out after your session ends to make sure that others cannot access your personal information.
